bestcompany.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy | Best Company

**Effective Date: January 6, 2017**

Please review this updated Privacy Policy carefully before using any of our services that link to this Privacy Policy. By using our services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect about you, how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed, how your information is protected, and how you can control the use and disclosure of your information. 

###  1\. Scope

This Privacy Policy covers BestCompany.com, LLC’s (“BestCompany.com”) print publications as well as online and mobile websites and applications that provide an authorized link to this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy applies to personally identifying information (“PII”) and other information collected about you and your devices. PII may include, for example, your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit/debit card information, user name and password, and demographic information. 

Our websites may contain links to third-party websites which are provided for your information and convenience. Please note that unless otherwise indicated, this Privacy Policy does not cover any information that may be collected through any third party website. BestCompany.com is not responsible for any content, terms and conditions or the privacy policies of any third-party websites. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads on our websites, including but not limited to third party advertisers, are independent third parties and are not affiliated with BestCompany.com. 

###  2\. Information Collected

Information you provide directly to us. You may provide different types of information to us when you access various content or features, post reviews or ratings, directly contact us, or otherwise interact with our websites, mobile sites or mobile applications, including: 

  * Contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and mobile number; 
  * User name and password; and
  * When you post a review or make a comment, information you provide such as your user name, email address, geographic location, and the content of your review or comment. 

Information we collect automatically. We may collect certain information automatically, including through the use of cookies (see below), web beacons, and other technologies. This information may include the following: 

  * Your browser and mobile device type, operating system and name of your Internet service provider; 
  * Web pages you visit;
  * Geo-location information;
  * Information about your interactions with email messages, such as whether the messages were opened and the links clicked in those emails; and 
  * Standard server log information.

Like most standard website servers, we also use log files. Log files track anonymous user information including, but not limited to internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is tracked in order to analyze trends, administer our websites, track users’ movements in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information tracked via log files is not linked to personally identifiable information except for IP addresses and source URL. 

Cookies. Our websites use a “cookie” to assign a unique identifier to your computer. The cookies we use are persistent files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies may be used to help save information on past activities and other preferences, so that you are not required to reenter information each time that you visit our websites, and to deliver content specific to your interests. 

Information we obtain from other sources. We may collect information about you from other sources, including when you use social media integrated with our products and services (for example, on our pages on Facebook) and when you were to purchase products and services from third party services. Examples of the type of information we may receive from other sources are user name and password and payment card information and demographic and lifestyle information. 

Combining Information. Please note that the information we collect about you may be combined or supplemented with information from other sources, such as information to validate or update your address, payment card or demographic information. 

###  3\. Use of Information

Information we collect is used for a variety of purposes. We may use this information internally or for other reasons. Any personal information that you supply to us remains your personal property. However, by submitting your information to our websites, you grant BestCompany.com and any third-party affiliates or subsidiaries of BestCompany.com the right to use that information for marketing purposes, and agree to receive email marketing from our website. We may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. We may share, license or sell your information to third parties for various marketing purposes, including but not limited to e-mail marketing, telemarketing, text messaging, and direct mail. 

###  4\. Disclosure of Information

User Reviews. If you submit reviews, we may share your submissions with other websites or provide links to your submissions from other websites and we may share your information with third parties. By submitting your email address to our websites you agree to receive email marketing from BestCompanies.com and our affiliated websites. We are able to offer third party services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers. 

Direct-Mail and Other Promotional Offers. We may share certain information about you for direct mail and other promotional offers. 

Authorized Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your information with third party service providers who help us with specialized services, such as mail and e-mail distribution, mobile messaging, website hosting, monitoring of user reviews and ratings, digital publishing, and analytics. We provide these companies only with the information they need to perform their services. 

Business Transfers. We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of one or more of our businesses, a merger, the creation of a separate business to provide certain of our products and services, the sale or pledge of our assets, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership. Information about our customers, donors, and other users of our websites and other products and services may also be shared in connection with a transaction in which BestCompany.com or one of our affiliates, is seeking financing, investment, support, or funding. 

If we engage in any of these types of transactions, your information will be subject to our privacy policy in effect at the time of the transfer of that information. 

Legal Requirements. We may disclose your information if required by law, such as to comply with a court order or subpoena. 

Protect our Websites and Users. We may also disclose your information to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or any violation of the User Agreement or to protect and defend the legal rights and safety of our websites and our employees, agents and contractors (including to enforce our agreements) or in connection with any safety or security concerns. Moreover, you hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when BestCompany.com, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time. 

###  5\. Opt out

Opting out online

You can opt out of receiving email communications from us by following the instructions provided at the bottom of each email. If you use this method, you will stop receiving only that particular type of email message. Unsubscribing from one list will not automatically unsubscribe you from all email lists. We only send email marketing to individuals that have agreed, whether by visiting our websites or through third party websites, to receive email marketing from BestCompany.com or its affiliates and partners. Please allow up to 10 business days for changes to your email preferences to take effect. During that time, you may continue to receive email communications from us that were already in process. 

Opting out by calling or writing

Another way you can opt out of receiving future communications from us is to write us at the following address: 475 E 1000 S, Pleasant Grove, Utah 84062 

If you are writing to us, please include your full name, and email address, and specify which type of promotional communications you no longer wish to receive. 

Cookies

We or our service providers may collect tracking information through cookies. You can opt out of accepting cookies or disable them from your browser. The Help function on most browsers contains information on how you can set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or can disable them entirely. If you opt out of cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of various features of our websites that are available to other users. For example, we may use cookies to recognize you by name when you return to this site so you don’t have to login again and provide your password. 

###  6\. Protection of Information

All collective information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, access to this information is strictly limited, and the information is not accessible to the public. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we use appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. In addition, we have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. 

Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable technological precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

###  7\. Third Party Sites and Services

This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to us. We recommend that you review their policies before you visit those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. We work with third parties, such as ad networks, analytics companies and social networking platforms, and they may collect information about your online activities over time and across our sites and other online services. 

###  8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will update the "Effective Date" posted at the top of this webpage. By using our websites after the effective date of such revision, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy with respect to any information collected after such effective date, provided that we will obtain your affirmative consent where legally required. 

###  9\. Your California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to whom certain information has been disclosed during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please write to us at: 475 E 1000 S, Pleasant Grove, Utah 84062 support@bestcompany.com. 

For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request and include the name of the CR website with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. 

###  10\. Privacy Protection for Children

Our services are directed toward a general audience and are intended for adults only. Visitors under 18 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information on our websites. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of 18. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

###  11\. Visitors from Outside the United States

BestCompany.com is a Utah limited liability company headquartered in Utah, USA. If you are located outside of the United States, the personal information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States and governed by applicable U.S. laws and regulations and this Privacy Policy. Some of this information may be transferred to and processed and stored by our service providers in other countries. By submitting your personal information to us, you consent to its transfer to and storage in the United States and other countries designated by BestCompany.com, its governance by U.S. laws and regulations, and its use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

###  12\. Questions regarding this Privacy Policy

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or would like a written copy, please contact us at: 475 E 1000 S, Pleasant Grove, Utah 84062 

Or, if you would like to contact us via e-mail, please direct email communications to support@bestcompany.com. 

###  13\. Disputes

Any disputes regarding this Privacy Policy are subject to our Terms and Conditions and will be governed by the laws of the State of Utah, applicable to agreements made and performed in Utah.
